Guide to the Fashion Moda Archive MSS.091
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Artists, Exhibitions, and Related Material, 112471
  - Subseries B: Articles, Press Releases, Flyers, and Announcements., 112832
    - Show announcements, n. d., undated; cuid9164; 112834 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Show announcements for other galleries., undated; cuid9165; 112833 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Subseries C: Photographs, 112763
    Series III Subseries C, Photographs, contains photographs covering exhibition openings, artworks, artists, Fashion Moda's neighborhood, and performances.
    - Ahearn, John: cast making., undated; cuid9166; 112831 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Agent., undated; cuid9167; 112830 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Animals Living in the City, Christy Rupp., undated; cuid9168; 112829 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Archeology, Liz n' Val, October 26 - November 23, 1991., cuid9169; 112828 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Artist collective & community members video, March 10, 1979., cuid9170; 112827 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Aspen Colorado Show [see also I. 1. 34], undated; cuid9171; 112826 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Brasz, Mark, undated; cuid9172; 112825 (Box 6, Folder 6A.)
    - Buggiani, Paolo [see also I. 1. 7], undated; cuid9173; 112824 (Box 6, Folder 6B.)
    - California billboards, 1980 - 1981 [see also I. 1. 17 and III. F. 15. slides 36-38], cuid9174; 112823 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Camouflaged Panzerism, undated; cuid9175; 112822 (Box 6, Folder 7A.)
    - Clark, Elizabeth: "Reconstruction", 1980; cuid9176; 112821 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Collins, Marshall: "World of Dinosaur", November 23 & December 6, 1983; cuid9177; 112820 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Contact Sheets., undated; cuid9178; 112819 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Cooper, Jerome., undated; cuid9179; 112818 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Daze, undated; cuid9180; 112817 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - De Mille, Arnette, undated; cuid9181; 112816 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Dejon, undated; cuid9182; 112815 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Dickson, Jane: "City Maze", September 6 - October 4, 1980., cuid9183; 112814 (Box 6, Folder 14A)
    - Edwards, Marianne: July, 1980; cuid9184; 112813 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Expressions Africans, February, 1987 (?).; cuid9185; 112812 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Facade [see also I. 1. 40], undated; cuid9186; 112811 (Box 6, Folder 16A.)
    - Fashion Moda T-shirt, undated; cuid9187; 112810 (Box 6, Folder 16B.)
    - Fekner, John: "From the Monkey to the Monitor", November 13 - December 4, 1982; cuid9188; 112809 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Freedom, undated; cuid9189; 112808 (Box 6, Folder 17A.)
    - Fun Shots, undated; cuid9190; 112807 (Box 6, Folder 17B)
    - Graffiti Art: Australia, 1987; cuid9191; 112806 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Graffiti Exhibition, 1980 [see also I. 1. 15 and III. B. oversize 21. 14-18], cuid9192; 112805 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Graffiti Artist's from the Early 70's, May 1984., cuid9193; 112804 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Group shot including Brasz, Daze, Easy-G, Eins ,Haring and Headley, 1983; cuid9194; 112803 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Holmes, Victor:, 1988; cuid9195; 112802 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Holzer, Jenny: facade of Fashion Moda [see also I. 1. 22 and III. A. oversize21. 32B], undated; cuid9196; 112801 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Howland, Becky 1981 Image for South Bronx Poster., cuid9197; 112800 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Image for South Bronx Poster, undated; cuid9198; 112799 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Jones Baird, Stefan Eins, Mark Kostabi, 1985-1986; cuid9199; 112798 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - "Ladys Wrestling", June 14, 1980., cuid9200; 112797 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Lorenz, Patrice: "From Farrakahn to Fallwell", 1984; cuid9201; 112796 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Lubar, Cindy: "119 Comments", 1981., cuid9202; 112795 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - [item removed], undated; cuid9203; 112794 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Misera, Lisi:, 1991; cuid9204; 112793 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - [item removed], undated; cuid9205; 112792 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Moving Tent, South Bronx, 1979; cuid9206; 112791 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Music, people & other objects, at exhibition of Haim Steinbach, 1980; cuid9207; 112790 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Neighborhood, mostly 3rd Ave. Betw. 135 and 165 St., Bronx, NY, undated; cuid9208; 112789 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Owens, Ashley., undated; cuid9209; 112788 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Pesce, Victor: "Water colors and drawin", February 28 - March 21, 1981., cuid9210; 112787 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Place, Chuck Hamilton: Spring 1982., cuid9211; 112786 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Polly Ester Nation: "Jesus comes to the Bronx", March 1980. [see also I. 1. 7], cuid9212; 112785 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Poppitz & Santos., undated; cuid9213; 112784 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Reccha, Louis., undated; cuid9214; 112783 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Riviera, James, undated; cuid9215; 112782 (Box 6, Folder 40A.)
    - Rollins, Tim & KOS, 1985; cuid9216; 112781 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Rothschild, Gail: "Three Arches", October 6, 1984., cuid9217; 112780 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Sacchetto, Bruno:, 1980; cuid9218; 112779 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Schecter, Jill, undated; cuid9219; 112778 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Science and Technology Exhibition, 1982; cuid9220; 112777 (Box 6, Folder 44A.)
    - Sebrens, Sam:, 1986; cuid9221; 112776 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Schr, Beate Maria: "Bodysuits", 1993; cuid9222; 112775 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - [item removed], undated; cuid9223; 112774 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Smith, Mary Agnes:, 1985; cuid9224; 112773 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Spank., undated; cuid9225; 112772 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Steinbach, Haim, 1980; cuid9226; 112771 (Box 6, Folder 49A)
    - Stout, Nancy., undated; cuid9227; 112770 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - South Bronx Show, 1979 (?); cuid9228; 112769 (Box 6, Folder 50A)
    - Taylor, David., undated; cuid9229; 112768 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Toral, Tabo [see also III. C. 6. 30], undated; cuid9230; 112767 (Box 6, Folder 51A.)
    - Vulva, by G. J. W., Fall 1992 [see also I. 1. 45], cuid9231; 112766 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Wells, David: "Cranach Cutouts", 1981, others, cuid9232; 112765 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Unidentified photographs., undated; cuid9233; 112764 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Subseries D: Artworks, 112733
    Series III Subseries D, Artworks, contains artworks by Keith Haring, Andre Charles, Daze, Crash, Kenny Scharf, Koor, and others. Included here is the Fashion Moda Portfolio with works by Ronnie Cutrone, Crash, Daze, Leon Golub, and James Poppitz.
    - Aone: drawings, incl. for Documenta 7. [see oversize, Box 21- No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9234; 112762 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Brasz, Marc: drawing., undated; cuid9235; 112761 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Charles, Andre: "South Bronx Show", 1988; cuid9236; 112760 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Cooney, Robert: "Por Exxon For Kill". [see over oversize, box 22], undated; cuid9237; 112759 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Crash: drawing for Documenta 7, other [see also oversize, box 21- No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9238; 112758 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Daze: drawing., undated; cuid9239; 112757 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Eins, Stefan. [see also oversize, box 21], undated; cuid9240; 112756 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Fekner, John: drawing for Documenta 7, others [see also oversize, box 21 - No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9241; 112755 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - G-Man, drawing [see oversize, box 21], undated; cuid9242; 112754 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Haring, Keith; drawing for Documenta 7. [removed to oversize Box 21- No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9243; 112753 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Headley, Wendell: drawings, 1982; cuid9244; 112752 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Jackson, Isaac: art for Documenta 7. [No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9245; 112751 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Koor: drawing., undated; cuid9246; 112750 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Kostner, Arthur: drawings. [see over oversize, box 22], undated; cuid9247; 112749 (Box 6, Folder 13A.)
    - Mullican, Mat [see oversize box 21], undated; cuid9248; 112748 (Box 6, Folder 13B.)
    - Nenner, Paulette: drawing for Documenta 7 [No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9249; 112747 (Box 6, Folder 14, Box 24)
    - Pabon, Jorge: drawing., undated; cuid9250; 112746 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Pou, Alyson: collage for Documenta 7 [removed to oversize Box 21 - No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9251; 112745 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Ramos: drawing., undated; cuid9252; 112744 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Satanic Show [see also I. 1. 21], undated; cuid9253; 112743 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Scharf, Kenny: drawing for Documenta 7. [removed to oversize Box 21 - No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9254; 112742 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Steckel, Anita: photograph for Documenta 7. [No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9255; 112741 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Thomas, Kathleen: drawings., undated; cuid9256; 112740 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Toxic: drawing. [see oversize, box 21], undated; cuid9257; 112739 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Unidentified drawings. [see also oversize, box 21], undated; cuid9258; 112738 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - van Dalen, Anton: drawing for Documenta 7[removed to oversize Box 21 - No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9259; 112737 (Box 6, Folder 23A.)
    - Wells, David: drawings for Documenta 7. [removed to oversixe Box 21 - No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9260; 112736 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Y-Pants, drawing, undated; cuid9261; 112735 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Fashion Moda Porfolio with works by Ronnie Cutrone, Crash, Daze, Leon Golub, and James Poppitz. (In Mapcase), undated; cuid9262; 112734 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Subseries E: Printed Materials, 112709
    Series III Subseries E, Printed Materials, contains magazines, journals, and catalogs on artists such as Mark Kostabi, Ron English, Nancy Stout, and Amy Chaiklin. These items were found in the collection and do not necessary pertain solely to Fashion Moda.
    - Art Com: number 16, v. 4 #4, 1982., cuid9263; 112732 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Bomb: Spring/Summer 1985., cuid9264; 112731 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - The Bride Groom is Hear, 1976, cuid9265; 112730 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Chaiklin, Amy: "Wall-painting" book, 1983., cuid9266; 112729 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - [item removed]., undated; cuid9267; 112728 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - English, Ron: "Art is a Horrible Waste of the Imagination", 1988., cuid9268; 112727 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Events, New Museum: New York, 1981 [see also I. 1. 16], cuid9269; 112726 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - [item removed], undated; cuid9270; 112725 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Galleria Communale d'Arte Moderna, Bologna: "Arte di Frontera", March- April 1984., cuid9271; 112724 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Kostabi, Mark: catalog, 1986., cuid9272; 112723 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Mati et Mire, Isy Brachot, Paris: 1985., cuid9273; 112722 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Mickiemoda, Annie: "The Modamutations"., undated; cuid9274; 112721 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - New Observations, issue #71, October 1 - November 14, 1989., cuid9275; 112720 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - New Observations, issue #73, January 1 - February 14, 1990., cuid9276; 112719 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - New Observation, issue #75, April 1 - May 14, 1990., cuid9277; 112718 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Pflasterstrand, vom 31. 1 bis 13. 2. 1981, Germany., cuid9278; 112717 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Rammellzee: "Iconic Treatise Gothic Futurism... ", 1979, cuid9279; 112716 (Box 6, Folder 16A.)
    - Space Window, catalog, September 14 - October 6, 1997., cuid9280; 112715 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Stout, Nancy: "The Way We Were"., undated; cuid9281; 112714 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Unidentified printed materials., undated; cuid9282; 112713 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Virus, graffiti zine, Holland., undated; cuid9283; 112712 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Waxberg, Richard, undated; cuid9284; 112711 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Yarber, Robert, undated; cuid9285; 112710 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Subseries F[1]: Slides, 112698
    Box 7: 1978 - 1980
    - [item removed], undated; cuid9286; 112708 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Hill-Montgomery, Candance: installation, 1980; cuid9287; 112707 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - [item removed], undated; cuid9288; 112706 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Polly Ester Nation: "Jesus Comes to the Bronx", March 1980., cuid9289; 112705 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - May 1980., cuid9290; 112704 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Steinbach, Haim: Summer 1980., cuid9291; 112703 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Edwards, Marianne: Summer 1980., cuid9292; 112702 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Dickson, Jane: "City Maze", September 6 - October 4, 1980., cuid9293; 112701 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Sophie Calle, C. Ginsberg, November 25, 1980., cuid9294; 112700 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Cooper, Martha: Subwa, 1980; cuid9295; 112699 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Subseries F[2]: Slides, 112666
    Box 8: 1981 - 1983
    - Eyes and Ears Foundation, "California Billboards", 1980- 1981; cuid9296; 112697 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - California Billboards in New York, 1981; cuid9297; 112696 (Box 8, Folder 11A)
    - Pass, D.: "It's a Piece of Cake", 1980- 1981; cuid9298; 112695 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Yohai Andors, Rhoda: "Skeleton Paintings", February 6-28, 1981, cuid9299; 112694 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Optima Studio: New Orleans, Spring, 1981; cuid9300; 112693 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Pizzanello, Josephine, others, Fall 1981, cuid9301; 112692 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Graffiti: Summer 1981., cuid9302; 112691 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Contemporary Art Center, New Orleans: Summer 1981., cuid9303; 112690 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - South Bronx Art, Projects, Others: Summer 1981., cuid9304; 112689 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - de Mille, Arnette / Malca: Dance at opening of "South Bronx Art, Projects, Others", Summer 1981, cuid9305; 112688 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Larkin, Sara: "Scapes of Outer Space", September 1981., cuid9306; 112687 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - October 1981., cuid9307; 112686 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Pou, Alyson: "Measured Fantasies", November 1981., cuid9308; 112685 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Thomas, Kathleen: Fall 1981., cuid9309; 112684 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Wells, David: "Royal Hunt" and "Time Machine", Fall 1981., cuid9310; 112683 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Gutzeit, Fred: January 16 - February 17, 1982., cuid9311; 112682 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Spring Fever, March 1982, cuid9312; 112681 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Documenta 7: merchandise, May 1982. [No Duplication Allowed], cuid9313; 112680 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - South Bronx Show, Summer 1982., cuid9314; 112679 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Baca, Fred, Fekner, John and Leicht, Don: "From Monkey to Monitor", Fall 1982., cuid9315; 112678 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Graffiti Mural, 1983; cuid9316; 112677 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Haring, Keith: "Installation at Tony Shafrazi", 1983; cuid9317; 112676 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Golubovic, Vesna: Installation on E 146 St, Bronx, 1983; cuid9318; 112675 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Dragan Ilic: "Man with the Red Pencils", February 1983., cuid9319; 112674 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Seeno, Anson: "Watching", March 1983., cuid9320; 112673 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Fashion Moda Open House, July 23, 1983., cuid9321; 112672 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Pier 34, exhibition, Fall 1983., cuid9322; 112671 (Box 8, Folder 35a.)
    - Rheinberg, Raffael: September 1983., cuid9323; 112670 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Roloff, Stephen: "Paper Murals", September 25, 1983., cuid9324; 112669 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Collins, Marshall: "World of Dinosaurs", November - December 1983., cuid9325; 112668 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Daze, Keith Haring, Kenny Scharf, others: Mural at Houston and Bowery, NYC, 1983; cuid9326; 112667 (Box 8, Folder 38A)
  - Subseries F[3]: Slides, 112650
    Box 9: 1984
    - Touring Show, "Of the Streets", 1984 [see also I. 1. 34 and III. C. 6. 6 and III. B. oversize 21. 19-24], cuid9327; 112665 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Poppitz, James: tour and projects, 1983-1986; cuid9328; 112664 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Wahl, Anita: January 10 - February 8, 1984., cuid9329; 112663 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - [item removed]., undated; cuid9330; 112662 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Buggiani, Paolo: April 7-17, 1984., cuid9331; 112661 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Graupe-Pill, Grace:, 1984; cuid9332; 112660 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Cyphers, Peggy: "Modern Fossils", April 28, 1984., cuid9333; 112659 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Graffiti Masters Show: April 28 - May 19, 1984., cuid9334; 112658 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Niedzialek, Terry: July 1984., cuid9335; 112657 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - South Bronx Show: August 1984., cuid9336; 112656 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - South Bronx, ca. 1984, cuid9337; 112655 (Box 9, Folder 48A.)
    - Mulero, Lillian: "Real Politic", October 29 - November 16, 1984., cuid9338; 112654 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Lady Pink/Lady Heart: installation, November 1984., cuid9339; 112653 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Ellis, Darrel: "Drawings from my Father's Photographs", December 1984., cuid9340; 112652 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Edwards, Marianne:, 1984; cuid9341; 112651 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Subseries F[4]: Slides, 112636
    Box 10: 1985
    - A-One, Toxic, Koor:, 1985; cuid9342; 112649 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - P. S. 25: March, 1985; cuid9343; 112648 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Van II: March, 1985; cuid9344; 112647 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Chaiklin, Amy: March 9 - April 10, 1985., cuid9345; 112646 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Social Studies, Agent, Marc Brasz & James Rivera: April 20 - May 16, 1985., cuid9346; 112645 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Democracy at Work at 22 Wooster St.: May 31 - June 22, 1985., cuid9347; 112644 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Poppitz, James: Graffiti Desk at Fashion Moda, June 1985 [see also I. 1. 32]., cuid9348; 112643 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - South Bronx Show: June 15 - July 17, 1985., cuid9349; 112642 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Fiorucci: window displays, July 19 - August 1, 1985., cuid9350; 112641 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Expression African, September 1985., cuid9351; 112640 (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Eins, Stefan: November 1985., cuid9352; 112639 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Fashion Moda Benefit at Ronald Feldman, Soho, November 1-16, 1985., cuid9353; 112638 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Intentionally omitted, undated; cuid9354; 112637 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Subseries F[5]: Slides, 112621
    Box 11: 1985 - 1986
    - [item removed], undated; cuid9355; 112635 (Box 11, Folder 66)
    - Robert Grahm/Susan Springfield: December 1985 - January 1986., 1985 - 1986; cuid9356; 112634 (Box 11, Folder 67)
    - Tim Rollins and the Kids of Survival: January - February 1986., cuid9357; 112633 (Box 11, Folder 68)
    - Stout, Nancy: march 1986., cuid9358; 112632 (Box 11, Folder 69)
    - Pod: facade of Fashion Moda, March 1986 [see also I. 1. 40], cuid9359; 112631 (Box 11, Folder 70)
    - Sacchetto, Bruce: March 1 - April 12, 1986., cuid9360; 112630 (Box 11, Folder 71)
    - Images in Fiber & Cloth: April 1986., cuid9361; 112629 (Box 11, Folder 72)
    - Lowinger, Leslie: May 7, 1986., cuid9362; 112628 (Box 11, Folder 73)
    - Moet and Delta: facade of Fashion Moda, June - July 1986. [see also I. 1. 40], cuid9363; 112627 (Box 11, Folder 74)
    - South Bronx Show: June 21 - August 1, 1986., cuid9364; 112626 (Box 11, Folder 75)
    - Pieces Sold: June 1986., cuid9365; 112625 (Box 11, Folder 76)
    - [item removed], undated; cuid9366; 112624 (Box 11, Folder 77)
    - Art for Money Benefit, December 1986, cuid9367; 112623 (Box 11, Folder 78)
    - Police Officers from local precinct: Installation, n. d., undated; cuid9368; 112622 (Box 11, Folder 78A)
  - Subseries F[6]: Slides, 112607
    Box 12: 1987 - 1993
    - Unidentified, 1986; cuid9369; 112620 (Box 12, Folder 79)
    - Unidentified exhibition, July 1987., cuid9370; 112619 (Box 12, Folder 80)
    - South Bronx Show: 1987., cuid9371; 112618 (Box 12, Folder 81)
    - [item removed], undated; cuid9372; 112617 (Box 12, Folder 82)
    - Corn, Thom: 1988., cuid9373; 112616 (Box 12, Folder 83)
    - Wibmer, Margret; March 29 - April 15, 1988., cuid9374; 112615 (Box 12, Folder 84)
    - Lens, Jessica: "The Sun, the Moon, and the Connected Stars... ", June 15-28, 1988., cuid9375; 112614 (Box 12, Folder 85)
    - Smith, Barbara: "Pageant of the Holy Squash", December 1988., cuid9376; 112613 (Box 12, Folder 86)
    - Back Room: January 1989., cuid9377; 112612 (Box 12, Folder 87)
    - New location: January 1989, cuid9378; 112611 (Box 12, Folder 87A)
    - Toral, Tabo: facade of Fashion Moda, 1989; cuid9379; 112610 (Box 12, Folder 88)
    - Misera, Lisi: Installation, 1989; cuid9380; 112609 (Box 12, Folder 88A)
    - Unidentified Slides, undated; cuid9381; 112608 (Box 12, Folder 91)
  - Subseries F[7]: Slides, 112565
    Box 13: Individual Artists A-K.
    - Ahearn, John, undated; cuid9382; 112606 (Box 13, Folder 92)
    - Anderson, Laura, undated; cuid9383; 112605 (Box 13, Folder 93)
    - Applebroog, Ida., undated; cuid9384; 112604 (Box 13, Folder 94)
    - Beuys, Joseph, undated; cuid9385; 112603 (Box 13, Folder 94A.)
    - Bieber, Lorna., undated; cuid9386; 112602 (Box 13, Folder 95)
    - Brasz, Mark, undated; cuid9387; 112601 (Box 13, Folder 96)
    - Brown, Marion., undated; cuid9388; 112600 (Box 13, Folder 97)
    - Buggiani, Paolo, undated; cuid9389; 112599 (Box 13, Folder 97A)
    - Chaiklin, Amy., undated; cuid9390; 112598 (Box 13, Folder 98)
    - Charles, Andre., undated; cuid9391; 112597 (Box 13, Folder 99)
    - Cohen, Helen., undated; cuid9392; 112596 (Box 13, Folder 100)
    - Colescott, Robert., undated; cuid9393; 112595 (Box 13, Folder 101)
    - Collins, Marshall, undated; cuid9394; 112594 (Box 13, Folder 101A.)
    - Corn, Thom., undated; cuid9395; 112593 (Box 13, Folder 102)
    - Crash., undated; cuid9396; 112592 (Box 13, Folder 103)
    - Crawford, Lonnie & Cutrone., undated; cuid9397; 112591 (Box 13, Folder 104)
    - Daze., undated; cuid9398; 112590 (Box 13, Folder 105)
    - de Preter, Jon., undated; cuid9399; 112589 (Box 13, Folder 106)
    - Dickson, Jane., undated; cuid9400; 112588 (Box 13, Folder 107)
    - Drew, Nancy, undated; cuid9401; 112587 (Box 13, Folder 107A.)
    - Eins, Stefan., undated; cuid9402; 112586 (Box 13, Folder 108)
    - English, Ron., undated; cuid9403; 112585 (Box 13, Folder 109)
    - [item removed]., undated; cuid9404; 112584 (Box 13, Folder 110)
    - Fekner, John., undated; cuid9405; 112583 (Box 13, Folder 111)
    - Finn, David., undated; cuid9406; 112582 (Box 13, Folder 112)
    - Freedom, undated; cuid9407; 112581 (Box 13, Folder 112A.)
    - Fun shots of Fashion Moda., undated; cuid9408; 112580 (Box 13, Folder 113)
    - Futura 2000, undated; cuid9409; 112579 (Box 13, Folder 113A)
    - Gadea, Patricia., undated; cuid9410; 112578 (Box 13, Folder 114)
    - Hambleton, Richard., undated; cuid9411; 112577 (Box 13, Folder 115)
    - Haring, Keith., undated; cuid9412; 112576 (Box 13, Folder 116)
    - Harris, Tim., undated; cuid9413; 112575 (Box 13, Folder 117)
    - Headley, Wendell., undated; cuid9414; 112574 (Box 13, Folder 118)
    - Hertz, Betti-Sue., undated; cuid9415; 112573 (Box 13, Folder 119)
    - Hill-Montgomery, Candace., undated; cuid9416; 112572 (Box 13, Folder 120)
    - Hoffman, Wendy., undated; cuid9417; 112571 (Box 13, Folder 121)
    - Ilic, Dragan, undated; cuid9418; 112570 (Box 13, Folder 121A.)
    - Jordan, Ariel Orr., undated; cuid9419; 112569 (Box 13, Folder 122)
    - Jones, Kim, undated; cuid9420; 112568 (Box 13, Folder 123)
    - Kostabi, Mark., undated; cuid9421; 112567 (Box 13, Folder 124)
    - Ladda, Justen., undated; cuid9422; 112566 (Box 13, Folder 124A.)
  - Subseries F[8]: Slides, 112530
    Box 14: Individual Artists L-Z
    - Quinones, Lee, undated; cuid9423; 112564 (Box 14, Folder 125)
    - Lewis, Joe., undated; cuid9424; 112563 (Box 14, Folder 126)
    - Lowinger, Leslie., undated; cuid9425; 112562 (Box 14, Folder 127)
    - Mann, Frank, undated; cuid9426; 112561 (Box 14, Folder 127A.)
    - Nadel, Jeremy., undated; cuid9427; 112560 (Box 14, Folder 128)